Love, Lust, Art and Religion
Sirens is a comedy, drama film directed by John Duigan.
In 1930s Australia, Anglican clergyman Anthony Campion and his prim wife, Estella, are asked to visit noted painter
Norman Lindsay, whose planned contribution to an international art exhibit is considered blasphemous.
While Campion and Lindsay debate, Estella finds herself drawn to the three beautiful models sitting
for the painter's current work, freethinking Sheela, sensual Pru and virginal Giddy.
Anthony Campion, played by Hugh Grant.
Estella Campion, played by Tara Fitzgerald.
Norman Lindsay, played by Sam Neill.
Sheela, played by Elle Macpherson.
Giddy, played by Portia De Rossi.
Pru, played by Kate Fischer.
Sirens is a 1994 film, based on the life of artist and author Norman Lindsay, written and
directed by John Duigan and set in Australia during the interwar period.
Sirens was mostly filmed at the Norman Lindsay Gallery and Museum, Lindsay's home and
studio in Faulconbridge, New South Wales and the town of Sofala near Bathurst.
Sirens, Four Weddings and a Funeral and Bitter Moon—all released in the US within weeks of one
another—were the films that brought Hugh Grant to the attention of American audiences.
The film explores themes of married couple, pastor,
painting, seduction, drawing and painting.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.